And, you know, it's a very powerful tool.
Especially compared to its competitors in this day
that we're in, you know, Microsoft designer is a pretty
complete tool and also mentioning that Microsoft
has not had any kind of experience with having
powerful design tools like Adobe, you know?
Because, you know, if Adobe had created something like this,
we'd be like, okay, this is what we predicted, you know?
But when it comes to Microsoft, the point that they have not
had previous any kind of previous experiences with
successful design products makes this product very
weird because it has been a success, you know, obviously.